no one knows what the world will look
like at the end of 2017 but one thing is
certain is that Star Wars The Last Jedi
comes out December 15th and I for one
have ruined multiple pairs of Underpants
in
anticipation I just a couple uh well the
intergalactic hype machine is already
fully operational and a recently
deployed Japanese pamphlet has start up
a jaa's nest of speculation as reported
by Star Wars news the print ad reads the
most shocking truth in Star Wars history
will soon be revealed uh wow you mean
we're finally going to learn W's
gender reach in and grab my
ovaries comedians let's try to beat
Disney to the punch tell me all the
shocking truths we are going to learn in
The Last Jedi in 60 seconds and begin
yes Tony Obi-Wan Kenobi is in a band
called Obi-Wan Direction all right
points
Tim all the droids piss and sh all
right Paul Darth Vader's full name is
Darth alamu yes Bo Tim kylo Ren is
boning Lena Dunham all right points Tony
uh the Cantina Band has actually been
replaced by The Mighty Mighty Boss Tones
playing that one song all right points
really going after the Boss Tones
Tonight
Tony Han Solo comes back to life as
Harrison Ford's character from Sabrina
all right points thans for that Paul F
the Death Star plans were actually a
blueprint for friendship a
points